Opened register 101
A customer entered
Queued a customer with free register 101
Invalid operation
Error: too few arguments
A customer entered
No free registers
Error: too many arguments
Opened register 102
Queued a customer with free register 102
Error: register 102 is already open
Departed a customer at register ID 101 at 118
A customer entered
Queued a customer with free register 101
Departed a customer at register ID 102 at 145
Departed a customer at register ID 101 at 168
Closed register 101
Error: register 103 is not open
Closed register 102

